Guide to the Vassar College Facilities Operations Records, 1800s-2021 (bulk 1908-1999)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series I. Administrative Files, 1879-2011
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Addendum Number 1 to the Contract Documents and Specifications to an All College Dining Hall for Vassar College, 1971 (Box 67)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] [College Dining Hall Plans and Drawings], 1971-1973; (2 folders) (Box 67)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] [College Dining Hall] - Electrical, 1971 (Box 67)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] [College Dining Hall] - Sprinkler, 1971-1972 (Box 67)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] HVAC [College Dining Hall], 1971-1973 (Box 67)
  - [Book Store] Behind the Scenes in the Bookshop - Marion Bacon, undated (Box 67)
  - Chimney By Alphons Custodis, Erected 1908 [Plans] (Box 67)
  - [Central Heating Plant] Boiler House and Boiler Data [Plans], 1933 (Box 67)
  - [Central Heating Plant] Boiler House Number 5 - Babcock and Wilcox Co. 1921 Construction [Plans] (Box 67)
  - [Central Heating Plant] Setting Piping Plan for Tubular Boilers, 1923 (Box 67)
  - Motor Driven Traveling Crane With Grab Bucket Hoist [Plans], 1921 (Box 67)
  - [Central Heating Plant] Boiler House Layout, 1928 (Box 67)
  - Grounds - Map Showing Locations of Roads, Walks, etc. As Per Survey Dated July 30, 1926 (Box 68)
  - [Main Building] Drawing - Main Building Basement [Copy], 1968 (Box 68)
  - [Skinner Hall] Specifications and Report - Bludworth Voice Amplifier System, Belle Skinner Music Building, 1930 (Box 68)
  - [Faculty Housing] House for Miss Claudia Lyon - Specifications, 1949 (Box 68)
  - [Utilities - Heating and Cooling] Specifications - Steam Distribution System Renovations Phase IV, 1968 (Box 68)
  - [Utilities - Heating and Cooling] HVAC Valve Identification Chart, circa 1970 (Box 68)
  - [Utilities - Water] Water Shutdown, 1985-1986 (Box 68)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Vassar College Chemistry Building - Design Development Specifications, 1981 (Box 68)
  - Loeb Art Center - Requests For Information Log, 1991-1993; (2 folders) (Box 68)
  - Loeb Art Center - Punch list, 1992-1993 (Box 68)
  - [Chapel] Roof Repairs & Rehabilitation, 1952-1953 (Box 68)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Electrical Pull Sheets, 1984; (2 folders) (Box 68)
  - [College Center] Fiberboard Plans, undated (Box 68)
  - [Faculty Housing] Faculty Housing Sites - Triangulated Executed Contract Documents Receipts, 1965 (Box 68)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Vassar College - Distribution System Phase III (AC/DC Conversion), 1957 (Box 68)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Vassar College - Distribution System Phase IV Equipment Contracts and Plans, 1958, 1971 (Box 68)
  - [Faculty Housing] Dr. W.B. Hill Faculty Housing - Specifications, undated (Box 68)
  - [Powerhouse Theater] Specifications for the Drama Workshop, Vassar College, 1972; (copy 2) (Box 68)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] All College Dining Hall Sketches, 1971 (Box 68)
  - Vassar College Facilities Inventory Reports, 1971-1973 (Box 69)
  - Vassar College Facilities Inventory Reports, 1971-1973 (Box 70)
  - Photographs, 1965-1972; (22 folders) (Box 71)
  - Science Facilities Project - Polshek Partnership Portfolio, 2007 (Box 71)
  - Science Facilities Project - List of other considered portfolios, 2007 (Box 71)
  - Equipment - Condensor/vacuum pump, 1983 (Box 71)
  - [Avery Hall] Avery Hall Renovation Master Plan - Design Strategies Report, 1994 Apr 29 (Box 71)
  - Miscellaneous floor plans and seating charts, undated (Box 71)
  - [Olmsted Hall] Records in the Library of Congress relating to Olmsted work at Vassar (copies), undated (Box 71)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Students Building - Proposed design for E. Dodge Child Room, undated (Box 71)
  - [Faculty Housing] Faculty Houses - Building plans, interior and exterior, undated (Box 71)
  - Director of Grounds Files - Jeff Horst, circa 1977-2007 (Box 72)
  - Director of Grounds Files - Jeff Horst, circa 1977-2007; (26 folders) (Box 73)
  - Director of Grounds Files - Jeff Horst, circa 1977-2007; (46 folders) (Box 74)
  - [Alumnae House] News scrapbook, undated (Box 73)
  - [Kenyon Hall] Kenyon Hall dedication, 2006 (Box 73)
  - [Avery Hall] Renovation photographs, circa 1994 (Box 73)
  - [Library - Thompson] Library - Photographs, undated (Box 73)
  - [Library - Thompson] Library - Operations and photographs, undated (Box 73)
  - [General Manager] General Manager's notebook, 1925 Apr 20-Nov 4 (Box 73)
  - [General Manager] General Manager's notebook, 1925 Nov 5 - 1926 Sep 30 (Box 73)
  - [General Manager] General Manager's notebook, 1926 Sep 30 - 1927 Apr 7 (Box 73)
  - Ground's Department weekly reports, 1917 Mar-Jun (Box 73)
  - [Library - Thompson] Library Addition - Specifications, 1961 (Box 73)
  - Sunset Lake excavation photographs, 1977 (Box 73)
  - Correspondence, 1993-1997 (Box 73)
  - [Vassar College Farm] Farm property map, undated (Box 74)
  - [Vassar College Farm] Farm Field Station, 1995 (Box 74)
  - Vassar College Arboretum, 1936-1955 (Box 74)
  - Landscaping - Trees, correspondence, 1912-1914 (Box 74)
  - Landscaping purchases, 1925-1961 (Box 74)
  - [Observatory - Maria Mitchell]Renovation specifications and photographs, 1998-1999; (2 folders) (Box 74)
  - [Skinner Hall] Architectural plans, circa 1931 (Box 75)
  - [Skinner Hall] Equipment, 1929-1933; (5 folders) (Box 75)
  - [Skinner Hall] Building Budget, 1930s (Box 75)
  - [Skinner Hall] Kimball Organ Company, 1929-1932; (5 folders) (Box 75)
  - [Skinner Hall] Lighting, 1929-1930; (2 folders) (Box 75)
  - [Skinner Hall] MacCracken, Henry, 1929-1932 (Box 75)
  - [Skinner Hall] Mclelland, Nancy (Decorator), 1929-1932 (Box 75)
  - [Skinner Hall] Miscellaneous, 1929-1932 (Box 75)
  - [Skinner Hall] Organ inquiries, 1929-1932; (3 folders) (Box 75)
  - [Skinner Hall] Organ specifications, 1929-1932 (Box 75)
  - [Skinner Hall] Equipment and hardware, 1929-1932; (5 folders) (Box 75)
  - [Skinner Hall] Westchester Electrical Equipment, 1930; (2 folders) (Box 75)
  - [Skinner Hall] Specifications, 1930s (Box 76)
  - [Skinner Hall] Allen and Collens (Architects), 1930s; (7 folders) (Box 76)
  - [Skinner Hall] Anderson, Edgar V. (General contractor), 1930s (Box 76)
  - [Skinner Hall] Miscellaneous, 1930s (Box 76)
  - [Faculty Housing] Faculty housing - Warden (Pratt House?), 1944-1950 (Box 76)
  - [Faculty Housing] 81 Raymond Ave (D Cottage), 1979-1988 (Box 76)
  - Petition to NYS Dept of Transportation concerning arterial highway and Arlington Elementary School, 1975-1977 (Box 76)
  - Raymond Avenue (NY Route 376) Rehabilitation Project, 2005-2007; (6 folders) (Box 76)
  - Class of 1961 Centennial Tree Bench, 2006 (Box 76)
  - Matthew Vassar statue, 2005-2006 (Box 76)
  - Jenny Holzer bench project, 2004-2006 (Box 76)
  - [Main Building] Bell, 2005-2006 (Box 76)
  - [Sanders Physics] Architectural specifications, Physics Laboratory, circa 1921; (4 folders) (Box 76)
  - [Sanders Physics] Mechanical specifications, Physics Laboratory, circa 1921; (2 folders) (Box 76)
  - [Sanders Physics] Plumbing specifications, Physics Laboratory, circa 1921; (2 folders) (Box 76)
  - [Sanders Physics] Construction specifications, Physics Laboratory, circa 1921; (3 folders) (Box 76)
  - [Sanders Physics] Correspondence, 1921-1925 (Box 76)
  - [Sanders Physics] Blueprints, circa 1921 (Box 76)
  - [Sanders Physics] Miscellaneous notes, circa 1921 (Box 76)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Chemistry Building - Proposal by Skolers & Lee, circa 1980 (Box 77)
  - [Main Building] Specifications and contracts for installation of storm windows, 1982 (Box 77)
  - Storm Windows specifications - Avery Hall / Alumnae House / Sanders Chemistry / Sanders Physics, 1982 (Box 77)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] "Vassar College Dining Hall: Analys of Contractor's Claim for Extra Costs…", circa 1973 (Box 77)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] "All College Dining Hall - Settlement Agreement with Rheinstein Construction", 1974 (Box 77)
  - [Library - Thompson] Library - Project manual, Vol. 1, 1974 Sep 4 (Box 77)
  - [Library - Thompson] Library - Project manual, Vol. 2, 1974 Sep 4 (Box 77)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] All College Dining Hall - Contracts and Specifications, 1971 May 13; (2 copies) (Box 77)
  - [Vassar College Farm] "Vassar Farm: A Nature Center Proposal" by the National Audubon Society, 1974 Sep 4; (2 copies) (Box 78)
  - [Vassar College Farm] "Vassar Farm: A Nature Center Proposal" by the National Audubon Society, 1975 Jun (Box 78)
  - [Olmsted Hall] Biological Sciences Building - Contracts and specifications, 1971 Jun 15 (Box 78)
  - [Olmsted Hall] Biological Sciences Building - Contracts and specifications, draft, circa 1971 (Box 78)
  - Ferry House schematic design by HB + FR, 2001 Oct 30 (Box 78)
  - [Ely Hall] Building specifications, circa 1889 (Box 78)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Students Building - Auditorium, 1912 (Box 78)
  - Landscape Master Plan, 2011 (Box 78)
  - [Faculty Housing] Pratt House, renovation, 2021; [2 folders] (Box 78)
  - [Faculty Housing] Pratt House, renovation sketches, 2021; [2 folders] (Box 78)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Sanders Chemistry - Clippings, 1908-1909 (Box 79)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Sanders Chemistry - Clippings and press releases, 1909-1978 (Box 79)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Sanders Chemistry - Correspondence, 1907 (Box 79)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Sanders Chemistry - Correspondence, 1908-1909 (Box 79)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Sanders Chemistry - Correspondence, Ewing & Chappell Architects, 1908 (Box 79)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Sanders Chemistry - Floor plans, undated (Box 79)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Sanders Chemistry - Negatives, undated (Box 79)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Sanders Chemistry - Photographs, undated (Box 79)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Sanders Chemistry - "Remarks given by Rev. Henry M. Sanders at the dedication of Sanders Laboratory", circa 1908 (Box 79)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Sanders Chemistry - "Statement of cost to build Sanders Laboratory", 1909 Jun 11 (Box 79)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Sanders Chemistry - "Words of Wisdom from Charles W. Moulton", undated (Box 79)
  - [Vassar College Farm] Proposed plans for Dairy House, undated; (rolled, very brittle) (Box 80)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Dining Hall - Negatives, 1972; (9 rolls) (Box 80)
  - Fire escape plans, undated (Boxes 81-82)
  - Miscellaneous oversized material, undated (Box 83 (Oversize))
  - [Alumnae House] Alumnae house, floor plans, undated (Box 83 (Oversize))
  - [Faculty Housing] 81 Raymond Ave (D Cottage), floor plans, undated (Box 83 (Oversize))
  - [Williams House] Architectural Drawings, 1923; (4 items) (Box 83 (Oversize))
  - [Library - Lockwood] Library - Lockwood Expansion, floor plans, 1995; (3 items) (Box 83 (Oversize))
  - [Library - Thompson] Thompson Library, architectural plans, Allen & Collins, Architects, 1903 Dec 12 (Box 83 (Oversize))
  - Unknown building, floor plans, undated (Box 83 (Oversize))
  - Concept sketch of Music Building, Sanders Chemistry, and New England Building, undated (Box 83 (Oversize))
  - Miscellaneous plan fragments, undated (Box 84)
  - Miscellaneous Folded Plans, undated (Box 85 (Oversize))
  - [Library - Van Ingen] Van Ingen Library Addition, Allen and Collens, circa 1936 (Box 86 (Oversize))
  - Miscellaneous Negatives, undated (Box 87 (Oversize))
- Series II. Plans, 1800s - 2010
  - Alumnae House, 1919-2004
    - [Plans] Alumnae House Proposal, 1919 (Roll Box 84)
    - [Plans] Alumnae House, 1920-1923, undated (Roll Boxes 85-87)
    - [Plans] Alumnae House Cross Section Through Dining Room, 1921 (Roll Box 98)
    - [Plans] Alumnae House Framing Plan, 1921 (Roll Box 99)
    - [Plans] Alumnae House Plan For Location of Building, 1921 (Roll Box 109)
    - [Plans] Alumnae House, 1921-1922 (Roll Boxes 83-84)
    - [Plans] Alumnae House Fireplace, 1921-1922 (Roll Box 99)
    - [Plans] Alumnae House Bay Window Return, [1922] (Roll Box 84)
    - [Plans] Alumnae House Roof, 1922 (Roll Box 93)
    - [Plans] Alumnae House Steel Service Stairs, 1922 (Roll Box 102)
    - [Plans] Alumnae House Washroom Details, 1923 (Roll Box 86)
    - [Plans] Alumnae House Dining Room Details, 1923 (Roll Box 86)
    - [Plans] Alumnae House Private Dining Room, 1923 (Roll Box 87)
    - [Plans] Alumnae House Linen Closet, 1923 (Roll Box 87)
    - [Plans] Alumnae House "Concrete Terrace Box – South Terrace", 1923 (Roll Box 91)
    - [Plans] Alumnae House Eaves, 1923 (Roll Box 92)
    - [Plans] [Alumnae House?], 1923 (Roll Box 93)
    - [Plans] Alumnae House Bathroom Details, 1923 (Roll Box 97)
    - [Plans] Alumnae House Corridor Steps, 1923 (Roll Box 98)
    - [Plans] Alumnae House Details of Entrance Doors, 1923 (Roll Box 100)
    - [Plans] Alumnae House Vestibule and Stairs, 1923 (Roll Box 102)
    - [Plans] Alumnae House Interior Arch Detail, 1923 (Roll Box 102)
    - [Plans] Alumnae House Basement, 1967 (Roll Box 97)
    - [Plans] Alumnae House, 1971 (Roll Box 214)
    - [Plans] Alumnae House 3rd Floor, 1971 (Roll Box 296)
    - [Plans] Alumnae House, 1923, undated (Roll Box 90)
    - [Plans] Alumnae Building - Proposed Plans, circa 1924, undated; (8 items) (Map Case - Drawer 57)
    - [Plans] Alumnae House, 1967-2004 (Map Case - Drawer 62)
    - [Plans] [Alumnae House?], undated (Roll Box 91)
    - [Plans] [Alumnae House?], undated (Roll Box 93)
    - [Plans] [Alumnae House?], undated (Roll Box 100)
    - [Plans] [Alumnae House?] Living room and Door, undated (Roll Boxes 88-89)
    - [Plans] Alumnae House, undated (Roll Boxes 92-93)
    - [Plans] Alumnae House, undated (Roll Box 95)
    - [Plans] Alumnae House, undated (Roll Box 97)
    - [Plans] Alumnae House, undated (Roll Box 101)
    - [Plans] Alumnae House Area Gratings and Saddles, undated (Roll Box 97)
    - [Plans] Alumnae House Chimney Detail, undated (Roll Box 93)
    - [Plans] Alumnae House Details of Door Outside Private Dining Room, undated (Roll Box 100)
    - [Plans] Alumnae House Dining Room, undated (Roll Box 94)
    - [Plans] Alumnae House Elevations, undated (Roll Box 97)
    - [Plans] Alumnae House Framing and Floorplans, undated (Roll Box 96)
    - [Plans] Alumnae House Front Entrance, undated (Roll Box 94)
    - [Plans] Alumnae House Main Stairs, undated (Roll Box 96)
    - [Plans] Alumnae House Millwork Details, undated (Roll Box 97)
    - [Plans] Alumnae House Millwork Details?, undated (Roll Box 96)
    - [Plans] Alumnae House Plot Plan, undated (Roll Box 87)
    - [Plans] Alumnae House Second Tier Framing Plan, undated (Roll Box 98)
    - [Plans] Alumnae House Steamlines, undated (Roll Box 93)
  - Athletics Facilities, 1974-2003
    - [Plans] Sports Complex, 1974 (Roll Box 217)
    - [Plans] Physical Education Complex Alternate Proposal, 1978 (Roll Box 277)
    - [Plans] Hudson River Rowing Association / Boathouse, 2000-2003 (Map Case - Drawer 89)
    - [Plans] Athletics and Fitness Center (AFC), undated (Map Case - Drawer 63)
    - [Plans] Athletics Facilities - Boat House/River Property, Prentiss Field, undated (Map Case - Drawer 64)
    - [Plans] Plan for concrete tennis courts, undated; (1 item) (Map Case - Drawer 57)
  - Athletics Facilities - Walker Field House, 1981
    - [Plans] Athletics Facility, 1981 (Roll Boxes 60-63)
    - [Plans] Athletics Facility, 1981 (Roll Box 214)
    - [Plans] Athletics Facility, 1981 (Roll Box 218)
    - [Plans] Walker Field House, undated (Map Case - Drawer 63)
  - Baldwin Hall (Infirmary), 1938-1961
    - [Plans] Baldwin, 1938 (Roll Box 215)
    - [Plans] Baldwin Hall, 1938-1939 (Map Case - Drawer 61)
    - [Plans] Baldwin Steam Service Plan, 1939 (Roll Box 230)
    - [Plans] Baldwin, 1939 (Roll Box 231)
    - [Plans] [Baldwin] Infirmary, 1939 (Roll Box 266)
    - [Plans] [Baldwin] New Infirmary Proposed Electrical Service, 1939 (Roll Box 262)
    - [Plans] Baldwin Hall, 1939-1940 (Roll Box 233)
    - [Plans] Baldwin, 1939, 1961 (Roll Boxes 264-266)
    - [Plans] Baldwin Infirmary - Proposed Plans, 1939, undated; (5 items) (Map Case - Drawer 56)
    - [Plans] Baldwin Infirmary - Proposed Plans, 1939, undated; (2 items) (Map Case - Drawer 56)
    - [Plans] Infirmary "Proposed Alterations", 1961 (Roll Box 53)
    - [Plans] Baldwin, undated (Roll Box 230)
    - [Plans] Infirmary, undated (Roll Box 231)
  - The Bayit (Jewish Student Center), 1999
    - [Plans] The Bayit (Jewish Student Center), 1999 (Map Case - Drawer 61)
  - Minnie Cumnock Blodgett Hall of Euthenics, 1916-1966
    - [Plans] [Blodgett?] Dining Room Detail, 1916 (Roll Box 171)
    - [Plans] Blodgett, 1925-1926 (Roll Boxes 212-213)
    - [Plans] Blodgett Hall, 1926 (Roll Box 211)
    - [Plans] Blodgett Floor Plans, circa 1926 (Roll Box 211)
    - [Plans] Blodgett Hall Detail Woodwork Livingroom, 1927 (Roll Box 144)
    - [Plans] Blodgett Apartments, 1927, undated (Roll Box 212)
    - [Plans] Blodgett Proposed Alterations, 1938 (Roll Box 319)
    - [Plans] Blodgett Hall Basement "DC to AC Conversion" (revised 1955), 1938, 1955 (Roll Box 247)
    - [Plans] Blodgett Alterations, 1956 (Roll Box 212)
    - [Plans] Blodgett, 1966, undated (Roll Boxes 216-217)
    - [Plans] Blodgett, undated (Roll Box 277)
    - [Plans] Blodgett, undated (Roll Box 279)
    - [Plans] Blodgett, undated (Roll Box 293)
    - [Plans] Blodgett Hall, undated (Map Case - Drawer 66)
    - [Plans] Blodgett Hall, undated (Map Case - Drawer 67)
    - [Plans] Euthenics Building, 3 views, undated; (1 item) (Map Case - Drawer 57)
  - Central Heating Plant (Boiler House, Coal Bins), 1916-2010
    - [Plans] New Boiler House Piping, 1916 (Roll Box 42)
    - [Plans] Boiler Room, 1916 (Roll Box 43)
    - [Plans] Boiler House, 1916 (Roll Box 43-44)
    - [Plans] Boiler Setting Plan, 1916 (Roll Box 49)
    - [Plans] Boiler House, 1916 (Roll Box 100)
    - [Plans] Boiler Plant, 1916, 1926-1927 (Roll Box 338)
    - [Plans] Boiler House, circa 1916-1917 (Roll Box 50)
    - [Plans] Boiler House, 1917 (Roll Box 41)
    - [Plans] Boiler House, 1917 (Roll Box 43)
    - [Plans] Boiler House, 1917 (Roll Box 46)
    - [Plans] "Coal Bunkers" F. Sutton, 1921 (Roll Box 41)
    - [Plans] Boiler House, 1921 (Roll Box 44)
    - [Plans] Boiler Room, 1921 (Roll Box 53)
    - [Plans] Boiler House, 1921, 1930, 1934 (Roll Box 48)
    - [Plans] Central Heating Plant, 1923-2010 (Map Case - Drawer 71)
    - [Plans] Boiler House New Pump Room, 1926 (Roll Box 43)
    - [Plans] "Fittings for Steamline", 1926 (Roll Box 44)
    - [Plans] Central Heating Plant, 1926-1985 (Map Case - Drawer 70)
    - [Plans] Boiler Plant, 1927 (Roll Box 44)
    - [Plans] VC Coal Handling Plant, 1930 (Map Case - Drawer 49)
    - [Plans] Boiler House, 1968 (Roll Box 293)
    - [Plans] "Ash Hopper Gate", undated (Roll Box 49)
    - [Plans] "Coal Pocket", undated (Roll Box 42)
    - [Plans] "Old Boilers", undated (Roll Box 49)
    - [Plans] Boiler House, undated (Roll Box 45)
    - [Plans] Boiler House, undated (Roll Box 47)
  - Chapel, 1930-1966
    - [Plans] Chapel Proposed Alteration to Tower, 1930 (Roll Box 265)
    - [Plans] Vassar Chapel Proposed Emergency Stairs, Coolidge, Shepley, Bulfinch, and Abbott, 1931 (Roll Box 248)
    - [Plans] Chapel Proposed Room in Tower, 1931 (Roll Box 268)
    - [Plans] Memorial Gateway to Chapel, 1931 (Roll Box 268)
    - [Plans] Chapel Alterations Rooms in Tower, 1931 (Roll Box 270)
    - [Plans] Chapel, 1931, 1952-1953, 1966 (Roll Boxes 267-268)
    - [Plans] Chapel - New Roof Supports, 1932 (Roll Box 269)
    - [Plans] Chapel - Proposed Chapel in Tower Vestibule, 1934 (Roll Box 264)
    - [Plans] Chapel – Proposed Chapel in Tower Vestibule, 1934 (Roll Box 271)
    - [Plans] Chapel Seating Chart, 1939 (Roll Box 297)
    - [Plans] Chapel Alterations, 1952 (Roll Box 271)
    - [Plans] Chapel Roof, 1953 (Roll Box 265)
    - [Plans] Chapel, 1953, undated (Roll Box 269)
    - [Plans] Chapel, 1966 (Roll Box 15)
    - [Plans] Chapel Alterations, 1966 (Roll Box 162)
    - [Plans] Chapel, undated (Roll Box 216)
    - [Plans] Chapel, undated (Roll Box 277)
    - [Plans] Chapel, undated (Roll Box 326)
    - [Plans] Chapel, undated (Map Case - Drawer 72)
    - [Plans] Chapel - Plan, undated; (1 item) (Map Case - Drawer 46)
    - [Plans] Chapel - Plans, undated; (2 items) (Map Case - Drawer 57)
    - [Plans] Chapel - Proposed Changes to Heating System, Never Made, undated (Roll Box 270)
    - [Plans] Chapel - Shepley, Rutan, and Coolidge, undated (Roll Box 260)
  - Chicago Hall, 1988
    - [Plans] Chicago Hall Improvements, Sasaki, 1988 (Roll Box 316)
    - [Plans] Chicago Hall Improvements, Sasaki, 1988 (Roll Box 321)
    - [Plans] Chicago Hall, undated (Roll Box 218)
    - [Plans] Chicago Hall, undated (Map Case - Drawer 73)
    - [Plans] "Original Drawings: Language Lab," Hutchins, Evans and Lefferts, undated (Roll Box 36)
  - College Center, undated
    - [Plans] Main Building - College Center, undated; (2 items) (Map Case - Drawer 60)
    - [Plans] College Center, undated (Map Case - Drawer 74)
  - Computer Center (Service Building), 1966-circa 1988
    - [Plans] Computer Center - Comptroller’s Office, 1966 (Roll Box 162)
    - [Plans] North Elevation Computer Center Proposed Entrance, 1966 (Roll Box 255)
    - [Plans] Computer Center, 1966 (Roll Box 300)
    - [Plans] Computer Center, 1966-1967 (Roll Boxes 308-311)
    - [Plans] Computer Center, 1966, 1984 (Roll Box 298)
    - [Plans] Computer Center, 1967 (Roll Box 279)
    - [Plans] Computer Center, 1967, 1982 (Roll Box 214)
    - [Plans] Service Building Floor Plan, 1968 (Roll Box 323)
    - [Plans] Computer Center, 1969, 1982 (Roll Box 322)
    - [Plans] Computer Center, circa 1988 (Roll Box 323)
    - [Plans] Computer Center (Facilities Operations), undated (Map Case - Drawer 77)
  - Russell and Janet Doubleday Studio Arts Building, 1992
    - [Plans] Studio Arts Building, 1992; (1 item) (Map Case - Drawer 53)
    - [Plans] Studio Arts Building, undated (Map Case - Drawer 131)
  - Ely Hall (Alumnae Gymnasium), 1902-2010
    - [Plans] Ely - Gym, Old - Plans, 1902, 1906, undated; (6 items) (Map Case - Drawer 54)
    - [Plans] Ely - Gym, Old - Proposed Changes (Folder 1 of 2), 1905-1922, undated; (15 items ) (Map Case - Drawer 57)
    - [Plans] Ely - Gym, Old - Proposed Changes (Folder 2 of 2), 1922, undated; (19 items) (Map Case - Drawer 57)
    - [Plans] Ely Hall First Floor "DC to AC Conversion", 1936 (Roll Box 261)
    - [Plans] Ely Hall, 1967 (Roll Box 363)
    - [Plans] Ely Hall, Aula, 1971-2010 (Map Case - Drawer 82)
    - [Plans] Ely Hall, 1990-1991, undated (Roll Box 363)
    - [Plans] Ely - Old - Plans, undated; (4 items) (Map Case - Drawer 54)
  - Facilities Operations Center (Buildings and Grounds Service Center), 1991
    - [Plans] Facilities Operations Center, 1991 (Roll Box 249)
    - [Plans] Facilities Operations Center, 1991 (Roll Boxes 254-255)
    - [Plans] Facilities Operations Center, 1991 (Map Case - Drawer 83)
  - Faculty Housing - General, [1891?]-1989
    - [Plans] 122 Raymond Avenue, [1891?] (Roll Box 105)
    - [Plans] 83 Raymond Ave - Professor Tredwell Residence, 1912 (Roll Box 192)
    - [Plans] 83 Raymond Ave - Residence for Professor Treadwell, 1912 (Roll Box 102)
    - [Plans] Map of Lands Owned By Estate of Samuel Sloan, Garrison, Putnam County (Lisburne Grange?), 1914 (Roll Box 115)
    - [Plans] [Rombout House] – also called "Pheil House" and "Eimer House on Flagler Farm" (Original and Alternative Proposals – not built), 1916 (Roll Box 172)
    - [Plans] 71 Raymond Avenue, Ella McCaleb House, Allen and Collens, 1916 (Roll Box 114)
    - [Plans] Palmer/Blanton House, 1927 (Roll Box 112)
    - [Plans] Palmer House, 1927, 1938, 1939 (Roll Box 110)
    - [Plans] John Peirse Residence College Avenue, 1930 (Roll Box 112)
    - [Plans] Residence for Prof. and Mrs. Vincent F. Hopper ("Lee House"?), 1939 (Roll Box 102)
    - [Plans] Unidentified Housing Project, 1941 (Roll Box 116)
    - [Plans] Fanny Borden House, 1941, undated (Roll Box 68)
    - [Plans] Plan for faculty victory gardens, 1943 Apr (Map Case - Drawer 57)